flightmyweb.com 2014-04-26

# Book Flights Tickets Online at http://flightmyweb.com

Mos Utility Pvt Ltd. requests all our users to read the ‘Privacy policy’ to understand how their personal and business information shared with us for travel services will be treated. We follow appropriate standards when it comes to protecting your privacy on our website. 

Mos Utility Pvt Ltd. collects Information from its user when they register to gain access or order to purchase any travel related services from our website. During the registration the travel data we store may include: Name, Address, and Email, travel schedules, seating preferences, accommodations, meal preferences and reservation information, as well as passport details that may be essential to fulfill regulation related to your travel. The Information you share with us is kept highly confidential, will be shared only on matters related to your travel.

Mos Utility Pvt Ltd. may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Mos Utility Pvt Ltd. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Mos Utility Pvt Ltd., the site or the users of Mos Utility Pvt Ltd., and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Mos Utility Pvt Ltd., the website or the public.

Mos Utility Pvt Ltd. also used cookies to provide user with better experience while visiting our website. Cookies are a small part of data which is stored on your web browser so that if you visit us again it will help us providing you with even better experience and cookies are only read by server.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

The Payments that you make through our online payment gateway is secured with the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption certified through our payment vendors. This means any online payment information you shared with us is transmitted through SSL which is a coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble the data before it reaches to us. 

This Privacy policy is subject to the change. Such changes would be updated in the website and readers are requested to go through privacy policy every time they log in. FlightMyWeb.in will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or enquiries within five business days of receipt.
